Guide to the Art Poster File ca. 1890-1910 PR55-1
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Book Posters, 2
  - Bernicia/ by Amelia Edith Barr (Wendell, S. Y.), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0397)
  - Books/ Romance History Travel, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0398)
  - The Bow of Orange/ A Romance of New York/ By Amelia Edith Barr (Hurd, L. F.), 1895/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0399)
  - The Boy Officers of 1812/ By Everett Titsworth Tomlinson, 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0400)
  - The Boy of the First Empire/ A Story-Life of Napoleon/ By Elbridge S. Brooks (Moores, A. J.), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0401)
  - Campaigning in Cuba/ by George Kennan, 1899/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0402)
  - Campfire Stories/ By Col. Edward Anderson (Olang), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0403)
  - Chiffon's Marriage/ By GYP (Heustis, Louise Lyons), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0404)
  - Chronicles of Count Antonio/ By Anthony Hope (Moores, J.?), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0405)
  - Chronicles of Count Antonio/ By Anthony Hope (Moores, J.?), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0406)
  - Cinderella and Other Stories/ By Richard Harding Davis, 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0407)
  - Cleg Kelly/ Arab of the City/ His Progress and Adventures/ By S. R. Crockett (Borie, A. E.), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0408)
  - Cuba and Porto Rico/ With the Other Islands of the West Indies/ By Robert T. Hill/ Of the United States Geological Survey, 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0409)
  - The Cuban and Porto Rican Campaigns/ Richard Harding Davis, 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0410)
  - The Damnation of Theron Ware or Illumination by Harold Frederic (Twachtman, John Henry (1853-1902)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0411)
  - The Days of Auld Lang Syne/ By Ian MacLaren (Hurd, L. F.), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0412)
  - Drawings by C. D. Gibson (Gibson, Charles Dana (1867-1944)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0413)
  - A Desired Holiday Book/ A Doctor of the Old School/ Ian MacLaren (Greenough, Walter Conant), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0414)
  - The Enchanted Butterflies/ By Adeline Upton Crosby (Clark, Mrs. S. H. and Crosby, Adeline Upton), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0415)
  - The Exploits of Brigadier Berard, a New Book by A. Conan Doyle (Hurd, L. F.), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0416)
  - Fettered Yet Free/ A Study in Heredity/ By Annie S. Swan (Hurd, L. F.), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0417)
  - Friday, the Thirteenth/ By Thomas W. Lawson, 1907/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0418)
  - "The Friend of the People"/ A Tale of the Reign of Terror/ By Mary C. Rowsell, 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0419)
  - Galloping Dick/ By H. B. Marriott Watson (Hazenplug, Frank (1873-after 1911)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0420)
  - Harper's Pictorial History of the War with Spain (Ogden), 1898/00/00-1899/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0421)
  - His Cuban Sweetheart/ By Col. Richard H. Savage and Mrs. A. C. Gunter (Gunn, Archie), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0422)
  - His Cuban Sweetheart/ By Col. Richard H. Savage and Mrs. A. C. Gunter (Gunn, Archie), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0423)
  - Houghton-Mifflin and Company's/ Holiday Books for MDCCCXCV, 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0424)
  - A Houseboat on the Styx/ By John Kendrick Bangs, 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0425)
  - In Ole Virginia/ By Thomas Nelson Page (Smedley, W. T.; Clinedinst, B. W.; Reinhert, C. S. etc.), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0426)
  - Mark Twain's Joan of Arc (Grasset, Eugene), 1894/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0427)
  - Joseph Jefferson's Rip Van Winkle/ Illustrated/ His Play Now First Published (McManus, Blanche (1870-after 1929)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0428)
  - The Jungle Book/ By Rudyard Kipling (Moores, A. J.), 1893/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0429)
  - Kemble's Coons (Kemble, Edward Windsor), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0430)
  - A King and A Few Dukes/ By Robert W. Chambers, 1896-1897 (Item PR-055-001-0431)
  - The King in Yellow/ By Robert W. Chambers (Chambers, Robert William (1865-1933)), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0432)
  - Kitwyk Stories/ Quaint Life in Holland/ By Anna Eichberg King (Edwards, George Wharton), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0433)
  - Kyzie Dunlee A Golden Girl/ By Sophie May/ 75 Cents Illustrated, 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0434)
  - A Lady of Quality/ By Frances Hodgson Burnett (Rogers, A. P.?), 1896/00/00-1897/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0435)
  - Legends of the Rhine/ By H. A. Guerber (McManus, Blanche (1870-after 1929)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0436)
  - A Lieutenant at Eight-een/ By Oliver Optic, 1895/00/00-1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0437)
  - Lilith/ A Romance/ By George MacDonald (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick (1873-?)), 1890/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0438)
  - Lippincott's/ Series of Select Novels/ Issued Monthly/ The Prince of Balkinstan (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0439)
  - Lippincott's Series of Select Novels/ The Spell of Ursula/ By Mrs. Rowlands (Newell, Peter Sheaf Hersey), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0440)
  - Little Daughter/ By Grace Le Baron, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0441)
  - The Little Huguenot/ By Max Pemberton, 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0442)
  - Lo-To-Kah/ By Verner Z. Reed (Dixon, Lafayette Maynard), 1897/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0443)
  - The Lottery Ticket/ By J. T. Trowbridge/ Start in Life Series, 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0444)
  - Lourdes/ Emile Zola's Greatest Book (De la Barre), 1894/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0445)
  - The "Maine"/ An Account of Her Destruction In Havana Harbor/ The Personal Narrative of Captain Sigsbee, 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0446)
  - Miss Grace of all souls/ By William Tirebuck (Walker, W. H.), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0447)
  - Albert Morris Bagby's New Novel/ Miss Traumerei (Reed, Ethel (1876-after 1900)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0448)
  - Mother Goose and Others in Wall Street/ By "Bond Man" (Bonte, George Willard (1873-?)), 1903/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0449)
  - Mrs. Cliff's Yacht/ Frank R. Stockton (Wells, E. B.), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0450)
  - Napoleon/ From Corsica to St. Helena, 1894/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0451)
  - New Books/ The Partner/ The Book of Athletics/ The Imposter/ The Mammoth Hunters/ The Ocala Boy/ The Wedding-Day Book (Schumacher, William E.), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0452)
  - North American Shore Birds/ A Reference Book/ By Daniel Giraud Elliot, F. R. S. E., 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0453)
  - On the Point/ Nathan Haskell Dole (Prendergast, Maurice Henry (or Pennell, H. B.)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0454)
  - Our Navy in the War with Spain/ John R. Spears, 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0455)
  - The Paying Guest (Morse, Alice Cordelia), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0456)
  - People We Pass/ Stories of Life Among the Masses of New York City/ By Julian Ralph (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0457)
  - Persian Life and Customs/ By S. G. Wilson, M. A., 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0458)
  - Picture Posters/ By Charles Hiatt (Hiatt, Charles), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0459)
  - The Pioneer Series of Original One-Volume Novels/ izmo, cloth, gilt top, $1.00 each, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0460)
  - Play in Province/ By Joseph and Elizabeth Pennell (Pennell, Joseph), 1893/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0461)
  - L. Prang and Co.'s / Holiday Publications/ Deep Blue Violets (Rhead, Louis John (1857-1926)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0462)
  - The Princess Sonia/ A Romance of Girl Art Life in Paris/ By Julia Magruder (Gibson, Charles Dana (1867-1944)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0463)
  - Compliments of the Printing Art (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0464)
  - The Purple Cow/ Vagaries Reprinted from "The Lark" (Burgess, Frank Gelett), 1895/00/00-1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0465)
  - A Question of Color/ By F. C. Philips/ Author of "As In a Looking-Glass" (Lincoln, A. W. B.), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0466)
  - The Red Republic/ By R. W. Chambers (Chambers, Robert William (1865-1933)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0467)
  - Royal Paper Dolls/ by Elizabeth S. Tucker, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0468)
  - Slain by the Doones/ By R. D. Blackmore (Hooper, Will Phillip), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0469)
  - Snow Bird and Water Tiger and Other American Indian Tales/ By Margaret Compton (Greenough, Walter Conant), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0470)
  - The Sorrows of Satan/ A New Novel By Marie Correlli/ Author of Barabbas (Gould, Joseph H. Jr. (ca 1875-1935)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0471)
  - The Sorrows of Satan/ A New Novel By Marie Correlli/ Author of Barabbas (Gould, Joseph H. Jr. (ca 1875-1935)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0472)
  - The Sprightly Romance of Marsac/ Molly Elliot Seawell (Verbeck, Gustave), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0473)
  - Stolen Souls/ By William Le Quex (Heustis, Louise Lyons), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0474)
  - Stolen Souls/ By William Le Quex (Heustis, Louise Lyons), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0475)
  - Stories of the Wagner Opera/ By H. A. Guerber (Hurd, L. F.), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0476)
  - Stories of the Wagner Opera/ By H. A. Guerber (Hurd, L. F.), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0477)
  - The Story of the Indian/ By George Bird Grinnell (Hurd, L. F.), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0478)
  - Taffy's Revised Football Rules (Anderson, F. Richard), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0479)
  - Three Gringos in Central America and Venezuela/ By Richard Harding Davis (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0480)
  - Three Gringos in Central America and Venezuela/ By Richard Harding Davis (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0481)
  - Tommy Atkins of the Ramchunders, 1895/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0482)
  - The True Mother Goose/ With Notes and Pictures by Blanche McManus (McManus, Blanche), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0483)
  - The Wally Pug of Why (Morse, Alice Cordelia), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0484)
  - The Watchfires of '76/ By Samuel Adams Drake, 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0485)
  - Statistics on War!/ Can be Found in the World Almanac for 1898, 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0486)
  - The Yellow Kid in McFadden's Flats/ by E. W. Townsend (Outcault, R. F.), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0487)
  - Yesterday in the Philippines/ By Joseph Earle Stevens, 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0488)
- Series III: Newspaper Posters, 3
  Series III, Newspaper Posters, contains 134 posters from 1895 and 1896. Posters primarily advertise New York daily and Sunday papers. A few posters from other East Coast cities are also included.
  Newspaper Posters are organized alphabetically by periodical, and then filed by date. Each poster has been assigned an item number based on that arrangement and are housed in flat files by item number.
  Artists, where identified, are listed in parantheses after the newspaper title.
  - New York Sunday Journal/ Bill Nye's Comic History of England/ A 10 Months Old Athlete (Brill, George Reiter), 1891/05/17 (1885, 1903?) (Item PR-055-001-0489)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ Thirty-Six Pages/ 3c/ Two Magnificent Colored Supplements Lithographed in Ten Printings/ Free (Brill, George Reiter), 1895/01/04 (Item PR-055-001-0490)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ The Xmas Journal/ "You Won't Be Happy Till You Read It." (Brill, George Reiter), 1895/12/22 (Item PR-055-001-0491)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ Blood-Stained New York/ One Soul in Two Bodies (Gunn, Archie), 1896/01/26 (Item PR-055-001-0492)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ Blood-Stained New York/ One Soul in Two Bodies (Gunn, Archie), 1896/01/26 (Item PR-055-001-0493)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ A Beautiful Four-Page Piece of New Music with Colored Cover, "Denny Murphy's Daughter Nell"/ Free With Every Copy (Brill, George Reiter), 1896/02/02 (Item PR-055-001-0494)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ Sleighing in Central Park, 1896/02/09 (Item PR-055-001-0495)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ Armenian Atrocities Surpassed/ A Baby's $500,000 Toys/ Pasteur and Koch Outdone, 1896/02/16 (Item PR-055-001-0496)
  - The Journal/ 40 Pages/ 300 Columns/ A Beautiful Twelve Color Awuarelle "Washington Arch, N.Y." (Gillin, P.), 1896/02/23 (Item PR-055-001-0497)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ Free with Every Copy A Beautiful Aquarelle "The Bowrey at Night"/ From the Original by W. L. Sonntag, Jr. (Brill, George Reiter/ From the Original by W. L. Sonntag, Jr.), 1896/03/08 (Item PR-055-001-0498)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ A New Dissipation of New York City Girls/ The Favorite Model of a Popular Artist (Brill, George Reiter), 1896/03/15 (Item PR-055-001-0499)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ A Beautiful Art Supplement "South Street" With View of Shipping/ 40 Pages/ 280 Columns (Brill, George Reiter), 1896/03/22 (Item PR-055-001-0500)
  - The Sunday Journal/ A Page of Reproductions of the Best Paintings at the Paris Salon/ Made by the Artists Themselves (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/04/12 (Item PR-055-001-0501)
  - The Sunday Journal/ Greatest Miracle of the Bible/ Proved by a Scientific Test (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/04/19 (Item PR-055-001-0502)
  - The Sunday Journal/ Easter Number (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0503)
  - The Sunday Journal/ Easter Number (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0504)
  - New York Sunday Journal/ Special Bicycle Number (Brill, George Reiter), 1896/05/10 (Item PR-055-001-0505)
  - Summer Resort Number of The Sunday Journal (Gunn, Archie), 1896/06/14 (Item PR-055-001-0506)
  - Sunday Journal/ New York/ All the News of the Summer Resorts (Gunn, Archie), 1896/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0507)
  - The Sunday Journal/ Never Mind Chimmie Tomorrow Yer Sells Journals and Yer Don't Get Stuck, See (De Yongh?), 1896/08/09 (Item PR-055-001-0508)
  - The Beautiful Supplement/ Will Be Given Free With the New York Sunday Journal/ "Why, This Ain't The New York Evening Journal", 1896/09/27 (Item PR-055-001-0509)
  - New York Journal's Colored Comic Supplement "In Gay New York"/ By Archie Gunn and R. K. Munkittrick (Gunn, Archie/ Outcault, R. F.), 1896/10/18 (Item PR-055-001-0510)
  - Wait for It/ It is Coming/ New York Journal's Colored Sunday Supplement (Gunn, Archie/ Outcault, R. F.), 1896/10/18 (Item PR-055-001-0511)
  - The New York Sunday Journal/ Best on Earth and Only 3 cents (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0512)
  - The Sunday Journal/ Special Christian Endeavor Supplement (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0513)
  - The New York Sunday Journal/ Photographed Miracles/ Deadly Explosive Fish/ The Female Shakespeare (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0514)
  - The Sunday New York Journal/ "Get off the Earth"/ Hello; Is That the Czar of Russia? (Gunn, Archie), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0515)
  - Sunday Journal/ New York/ Brighter Features/ More Striking/ More Originality/ The Very Best (Gunn, Archie), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0516)
  - The New York Sunday Journal/ Can you Wait Until Sunday Next for 40 Sensational Surprises?, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0517)
  - The Sunday Journal/ Shop Girls in Tights/ Is Bicycling Immoral?/ The End of the World All the News of the Summer Resorts (Upjohn, E. P.), 0000/00/00 (Summer?) (Item PR-055-001-0518)
  - The Sunday New York Journal/ The Best on Earth (Mayer, Hy.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0519)
  - The Sunday Journal/ The World Cut In Two!/ Has New York A Bastille?/ Alan Dale Has Hit It! (Mayer, Hy.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0520)
  - The Sunday Press Easter Number (Outcault, R. F.), 1895/04/14 (Item PR-055-001-0521)
  - The Press Bulletin/ Anniversary Number/ 8 Years Old, 1895/12/08 (Item PR-055-001-0522)
  - The Press Bulletin/ Anniversary Number/ 8 Years Old, 1895/12/08 (Item PR-055-001-0523)
  - The New York Sunday Press/ The Christmas Press, 1895/12/15 (Item PR-055-001-0524)
  - The New York Sunday Press/ Holiday Number/ Art Cover Printed in Brilliant and Dashing Colors, 1895/12/22 (Item PR-055-001-0525)
  - The New York Sunday Press/ New Year's Number, 1895/12/25 (Item PR-055-001-0526)
  - The New York Sunday Press, 1896/01/05 (Item PR-055-001-0527)
  - The New York Sunday Press/ Take Notice/ It's Lively and Sparkling (But Never Nasty), 1896/01/12 (Item PR-055-001-0528)
  - The New York Sunday Press/ 40 Pages/ This Poster is a Modest Example of the Sort of Color Work We're Doing Best in the Country, 0000/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0529)
  - The Sunday World/ How the Beef Trust Relentlessly Robs Us (Shaw, A.), 1895/04/14 (Item PR-055-001-0530)
    This item is housed in Oversize Folder 19
  - The Sunday World/ How the New Japanese Chinese Treaty Threatens Every Workingman (Shaw, A.), 1895/04/28 (Item PR-055-001-0531)
  - The Sunday World/ Usury Sharks and Their Shameful Extortions (Shaw, A.), 1895/05/05 (Item PR-055-001-0532)
  - In the Sunday World/ A Real Robinson Crusoe of the Present Day (Alder), 1895/05/19 (Item PR-055-001-0533)
  - The New York Sunday World/ A Wedding That Will Out-Million the Gould and Astor Weddings (Henderson (or Anderson)?), 1895/05/26 (Item PR-055-001-0534)
  - Exploring the Garden of Eden for Relics of Adam and Eve/ All in the New York Sunday World (Bing, H.?), 1895/06/09 (Item PR-055-001-0535)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Summer Resorts (McGibb, Tom), 1895/06/23 (Item PR-055-001-0536)
  - The New York Sunday World/ New Scientific Discovery!/ The World Makes a Chemical Analysis of Mosquito Poison, and finds it more deadly than strychnine, 1895/07/07 (1889,1901?) (Item PR-055-001-0537)
  - The New York Sunday World/ All the News and Gossip of the Summer Resorts (De Yong?), 1895/07/28 (Item PR-055-001-0538)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Danger! A Physician's Warning to Women of the Perils of a Fashion the are all Following (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)?), 1895/09/01 (Item PR-055-001-0539)
  - The New York Sunday World/ The Very Wickedest Town in America (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1895/09/08 (Item PR-055-001-0540)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Horrors Beyond Imagination/ The World's Special Commissioner Returns from Armenia with Most Appalling Evidence of Turkish Atrocities. (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick (1873-?)), 1895/09/15 (Item PR-055-001-0541)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Never Without a Very Surprising Feature/ Never Stupid or Sleepy, 1895/09/22 (Item PR-055-001-0542)
  - The New York Sunday World, 1895/09/29 (Item PR-055-001-0543)
  - The Sunday World/ New York Oct-6th/ More Howling Humor (Alder), 1895/10/06 (Item PR-055-001-0544)
  - The New York Sunday World/ High Life Revelries in New York (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1895/10/13 (Item PR-055-001-0545)
  - The New York Sunday World/ High Life Revelries in New York (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1895/10/13 (Item PR-055-001-0546)
  - The New York Sunday World/ New York "Society"/ A Truthful Picture of Who and What it is To-Day, 1895/10/20 (Item PR-055-001-0547)
  - The New York Sunday World/ How to Live on 25 cents a Day and Live Well! (Shaw, A.), 1895/10/27 (Item PR-055-001-0548)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Will Tell You The Latest Society Fad/ Describe an Experience Our "New Woman" Had (Upjohn, E. P.), 1895/11/03 (Item PR-055-001-0549)
  - The New York Sunday World/ The Most Marvelous Book Ever Printed/ It’s the New York/ Sunday World, 1895/11/10 (Item PR-055-001-0550)
  - The New York Sunday World/ New York Women Who Gamble in Wall Street (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick (1873-?)), 1895/11/17 (Item PR-055-001-0551)
  - The New York Sunday World/ New York's Most Needed Public Improvement to be Actually Realized at Last/ Society at the Opera (Upjohn, E. P.), 1895/11/24 (Item PR-055-001-0552)
  - The New York Sunday World/ A Most Remarkable Invalid (Flising, C. S. or Haskell, Ernest?), 1895/12/01 (Item PR-055-001-0553)
  - The New York Sunday World/ More Features, Surprises, Brilliancy, Editorial Genius/ Than all the Other Sunday Papers Put Together, 1895/12/08 (Item PR-055-001-0554)
  - The Great Christmas Number of the New York Sunday World/ 500 Columns 500!!, 1895/12/15 (Item PR-055-001-0555)
  - Don't Miss/ The New-York Sunday World (Upjohn, E. P.), 1895/12/22 (Item PR-055-001-0556)
  - Don't Miss/ The New-York Sunday World (Upjohn, E. P.), 1895/12/22 (Item PR-055-001-0557)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Sunday Dec 29th/ 1895-96/ Great New Year's Number, 1895/12/29 (Item PR-055-001-0558)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Sunday Jan 5th/ Remarkable Experiments to Test Your Nerves, 1896/01/05 (Item PR-055-001-0559)
  - New York Sunday World/ Funnier than Puck or Judge (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick (1873-?)), 1896/01/12 (Item PR-055-001-0560)
  - The New York Sunday World/ The Greatest/ In Notable Achievements!/ In Number of Pages!/ In Public Service!/ In Influence!/ In Circulation, 1896/01/19 (1890, 1902?) (Item PR-055-001-0561)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Don't Miss Next Sunday's World/ Striking Features!/ Beautiful Pictures!/ Howling Humor, 1896/01/26 (Item PR-055-001-0562)
  - The Sunday World/ Fun Will Be One Feature of Next Sunday's World, 1896/02/02 (Item PR-055-001-0563)
  - Sunday World/ New York Feb 9th (Outcault, R. F.), 1896/02/09 (1890, 1902?) (Item PR-055-001-0564)
  - The New York Sunday World/ 3 Magazines Combined with All the News Besides/ McDougall up in a Balloon (Russell, W. E.), 1896/02/16 (Item PR-055-001-0565)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Nell Bly as and Elephant Trainer, 1896/02/23 (Item PR-055-001-0566)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Man's Trials in Leap Year, 1896/03/01 (Item PR-055-001-0567)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Mr. McDougall's Insomnia/ Powers's Great Cartoon on Rapid Transit, 1896/03/08 (Item PR-055-001-0568)
  - The New York Sunday World/ How to Keep Husbands at Home (Saalburg), 1896/03/14 (Item PR-055-001-0569)
  - The New York Sunday World/ A Great Easter Number, 1896/03/22 (Item PR-055-001-0570)
  - The New York Sunday World/ Political April Fools Day, 1896/03/29 (Item PR-055-001-0571)
  - Sunday World/ April 5th/ Special::Harrison Wedding, 1896/04/05 (Item PR-055-001-0572)
  - "Say! Have You Seen This Week's Sunday World It's Great."/ Sunday Circulation Over 500,000 (Gihon, A. D.), 1896/04/12 (Item PR-055-001-0573)
  - The Sunday World/ April 19th/ Champion Zimmerman Edits the Bicycle Page/ Best Woman's Page Published, 1896/04/19 (Item PR-055-001-0574)
  - Sunday World/ April 26th/ Monsters That Live on Planet Jupiter, 1896/04/26 (Item PR-055-001-0575)
  - Sunday World/ May 3rd/ Zimmerman's Bicycle Page/ Woman's Fads and Foibles, 1896/05/03 (Item PR-055-001-0576)
  - The Sunday World/ The Latest Inventions in Animals, 1896/05/10 (Item PR-055-001-0577)
  - Sunday World/ May 17th/ Political Demonstration in Hogan's Alley, 1896/05/17 (Item PR-055-001-0578)
  - The Sunday World/ Hogan's Alley Pic-Nic to Coney Island (Gihon, A. D.), 1896/05/24 (Item PR-055-001-0579)
  - Sunday World/ Hogan's Alley Attacked by a Crowd from Hoboken, 1896/05/31 (Item PR-055-001-0580)
  - The Sunday World/ Municipal Baby Catchers/ Funny Cartoon (Edge, Gilbert F.), 1896/06/07 (Item PR-055-001-0581)
  - The Sunday World's Great Convention Number (Saalburg), 16/14/1896 (1885, 1891?) (Item PR-055-001-0582)
  - The Sunday World/ June 21st/ Bicycle Craze in Hogan's Alley, 1896/06/21 (Item PR-055-001-0583)
  - The Sunday World/ Why Dr. Parkhurst Needs a Rest, 1896/06/28 (Item PR-055-001-0584)
  - The Great Sunday World/ Convention Number, 1896/07/05 (Item PR-055-001-0585)
  - The Sunday World/ July 12/ 8 Funny Pages/ A Fierce Phase of Cannibalism (Edge, Gilbert F.), 1896/07/12 (Item PR-055-001-0586)
  - The Sunday World/ Hogan's Alley Children Take a Day in the Country (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/07/19 (Item PR-055-001-0587)
  - The Sunday World/ Opening of the Hogan's Alley Roof Garden (Edge, Gilbert F.), 1896/07/26 (Item PR-055-001-0588)
  - The Sunday World/ New Perils from Microbes, 1896/08/02 (Item PR-055-001-0589)
  - The Sunday World/ The Spectre Cow/ A Woman Dressed in Diamonds, 1896/08/09 (Item PR-055-001-0590)